

Hoang Bao Vo (Andy)

Date of birth: 19/09/1998 | **Nationality:** Vietnamese | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:**

(+84) 338705850 (Mobile) | Email address: andy.vo.98vn@gmail.com | LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/bao-vo-hoang | Github: https://github.com/andyvo190998 | Portfolio:

https://andyvo190998.github.io/animated-portfolio/

Address: 36 Bờ Bao Tân Thắng, 7600, Hồ Chí Minh, Vietnam (Home)

ABOUT ME

With more than 4 years of experience working with **NextJS**, **ReactJS**, **NodeJS**, **and Python**,... I am confident to handle most of the tasks related to web applications. I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, hard-working person who can be able to adapt to all challenging situations. I can work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. Please visit my **GitHub** repositories and **portfolio** website to see my work to learn more about me.

DIGITAL SKILLS

React, Next.js, React Native | typescrypt | Python | NodeJS | MySQL | Angular TS, Angular JS

WORK EXPERIENCE

10/12/2019 - 31/12/2020 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

SOLAR ENERGY ENGINEER SOLARBK

Research and find out new technologies that improve the efficiency of solar modules, receive feedback from clients and find the solution to fix that issue on Solar panels.

01/07/2021 - 01/10/2021 Singapore, Singapore

WEB DEVELOPERS FULLERTON HEALTH

As a part-time full stack web developer, I was responsible for maintaining, debug, add new features for their website by using ReactJS, NodeJS.

01/04/2023 - CURRENT Munich, Germany

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER KIUTRA GMBH

- Creating and maintaining front-end using ReactJS
- Making API using Flask, Quart, Websocket,...
- Creating and maintaining middleware using Python for interprogress communication
- Support, setup software application for hardware team

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/06/2016 - 01/10/2020 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

BACHELOR'S DEGREE Ho Chi Minh University Technology and Education

My major is material technology, more specifically, I study about some devices like Transistors, MOSFET, LED, Sensors, TCO,... nanostructure, simulation properties of materials, semiconductors, thin film technology,... deep knowledge of semiconductors and Transistor and General Electronics

Address 1 Vo Van Ngan, Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam, 71300, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | Website hcmute.edu.vn |

Field of study Physics, Chemistry, Physical sciences not elsewhere classified | Final grade GPA: 7.64/10 | Thesis Thesis: 9.6/10

MASTER OF SCIENCE University of Augsburg

Continues with the subjects of bachelor's degree, I keep digging deeper into Semiconductor Technology, and gain more knowledge of Semiconductor devices (E.g Transistor, Solar cells,...), understand the way it works and how to create it. Beside of that, I am learning the properties of other materials such as Metals, and polymer composites,...

Address Universitätsstraße 2, Augsburg, 86159, Augsburg, Germany | Website www.uni-augsburg.de |

Field of study Chemistry, Physics | Thesis The properties of Cul thin films prepared by spin coating.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **VIETNAMESE**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	B1	B1	B1	B1	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

HONOURS AND AWARDS

05/12/2021

Project Manager - Coursera

Those who earn the Google Project Management Certificate have completed six courses, developed by Google, that include hands-on, practice-based assessments and are designed to prepare them for introductory-level roles in Project Management. They are competent in initiating, planning and running both traditional and agile projects.

Link https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/UW5R4PX9ZCVV

28/12/2021

Web developer - Freecodecamp

From this course, i was learning a lot of basic knowledges about javascript and data structure.

Link https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc71b5460b-8133-41f4-94fc-5727c76f5015/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

26/02/2022

web developer - Udemy

This course guides me from front end to back end and including data base like MongoDB.

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-acdd3aa5-ddc5-4778-93b5-c2c5eee59f29.pdf